worldwidegolfshops.com 2017-07-31

# Privacy Policy

At Worldwide Golf Shops, we are committed to protecting the privacy and security of any personal information you provide to us. This Privacy Policy explains our policies and practices for collecting, storing, using, sharing, and protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect through this website, through your purchases of our products wherever they are sold, and through marketing and promotional activities that we conduct from time to time.

Along with our Terms of Use, this Privacy Policy governs your use of our Web site. We may update this Privacy Policy as we continue to improve the services, products, and features we provide to you and as new developments in technology, law, or regulation call for changes. Please check this Privacy Policy from time to time to make sure you stay current.

## How Your Information is Collected and Used

When you purchase items from us or voluntarily submit information to us (for example, when you sign up for an account with WGS, send us e-mails or subscribe to our e-mail promotions, participate in sweepstakes, contests, or surveys, or post information on our website), we may collect personally identifiable information from you such as your name, e-mail address, postal address, telephone number, and credit card number. We may use this information to provide you with the products and services you have requested, to investigate and answer questions or concerns you submit to us, to offer you opportunities to participate in promotional programs tailored to you, to list you as a winner of a contest or sweepstakes, or to notify you of information that may be of interest to you about Worldwide Golf Shops or our business partners and affiliates.

We may also collect non-personally identifiable information from you, (such as information regarding your interests, hobbies, preferences for products and services, and lifestyle) when you choose to provide it.

When you visit our website, we and our third-party service providers use a feature on your Internet browser called a "cookie" to identify you and enhance your experience on the site in various ways, such as by remembering your user name, password, and preferences, and tracking your click streams. Cookies are small files placed on your computer's hard drive. We and our third-party service providers use cookies and pixel tags to collect certain technical information from your computer when you visit our Web site, including your Internet Protocol ("IP") address, your computer's operating system, your browser type, and any referring Web site address. Most Internet browsers give you the option to reject cookies, but doing so generally hinders the browser's performance and will adversely affect your experience when using our Web site.

We partner with third-party Internet advertising companies, known as "ad networks," to serve ads for us across the Internet. Ad networks use cookies and pixel tags to collect information about your visits to our Web site and other Web sites so that they can deliver ads to you that may correspond to your interests. We do not share any personally identifiable information about you with these ad networks. If you prefer not to receive these ads, you may opt-out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative's opt-out page, at http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp.

We may also obtain information about you from third parties, including demographic information (such as number of household members, age, and gender), and purchase preferences. We use such information to improve the accuracy of our customer database, increase our understanding of our customers, and identify potential customers.

## How Your Information May Be Shared

We do not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to outside marketers. We may, however, share such information in limited circumstances, outlined below.

We may share your information with our subsidiaries, affiliates, and trusted businesses partners, so that we, and they, can provide products and services you have requested and information and offers that may be of interest to you. In addition, we may share your information with third parties that need access to the information to help us fulfill your requests for products and services. We require all parties with whom we share this information to comply with our standards of quality and to comply with our policies for safeguarding your information.

When we collect aggregate data that does not include personally identifiable information, such as demographic and statistical information, we may share that data with third parties.

We may disclose your information when we believe any applicable law, regulation, or legal proceeding requires us to do so, or when disclosure is necessary to respond to claims against us, to protect our customers, to report or collect debts owed to us, or otherwise to protect our rights and property.

If WGS becomes involved in a merger, reorganization, or bankruptcy, we may transfer or otherwise share your information in connection with that transaction or event. 

## How Your Information Is Safeguarded

We enforce reasonable and appropriate security measures to protect against any unauthorized access to or disclosure of your information. We maintain your information on a secured server behind a firewall. All data is encrypted, and all data related to our retail services is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer technology. Even as we strive to protect your information, however, we cannot guarantee that these or any other information security measures will be completely effective, and we cannot assume responsibility for the actions of parties who may gain unauthorized access to your personally identifiable information. Thus, WGS Company makes no warranties, express, implied, or otherwise, as to the ultimate effectiveness of our reasonable and appropriate security measures.

## Third-Party Web Sites

Our Web site may carry advertisements by third parties and links to the Web sites of third parties, so that we can make additional products, services, and information available to you. This Privacy Policy applies only to WGS, and we do not control the privacy policies and practices of third parties, which may differ from ours. Because third parties may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect their own data, or make their own solicitations of personal information from you, we encourage you to read their privacy policies before using their websites. We assume no responsibility for your sharing of information with these third parties.

## Accessing and Updating Personal Information

When you register with WGS, you can review, maintain, and change your own account information at any time. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we also depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

## Promotional e-Mails

If users wish to subscribe to our e-mail newsletters, we ask for contact information (such as name, e-mail address and, occasionally, demographic information). We use this information to provide you with information about special sales, promotions, and other offers that may be of interest to you, if at any time you choose not to receive these promotional e-mails any longer, you can unsubscribe by following the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each promotional e-mail. Please be advised that you may continue to receive e-mails from us until your requested change takes effect.

## Interactive Features

At some of our sites, we offer interactive and community features such as discussion boards, webcasts and user profiles. Note that all personal information sent or posted via such features becomes public information for which we are not responsible.

## Tell-A-Friend

If customers elect to use our referral service for informing a friend about our sites and services, we may ask them for the friend's name, job title and e-mail address. Worldwide Golf Shops will store and use this information to send the friend an invitation. This information may also be used to provide information about our company and related products and services. The friend may contact us as specified in the tell-a-friend message to request that no further communications be sent.

## Communication with Us

We have features where our customers can submit information to us (such as our Tournament Donation Request form). Where such submissions include requests for service, support or information, we may forward them to our agents, as needed, to best respond to the specific request. In addition, we may retain e-mails and other information sent to us for our internal administrative purposes, and to help us to serve customers better.

## Communications from Us: Service Updates, Special Offers

In order to best serve our customers, we may send updates that contain important information about our products and services. For example, we send new members a welcoming message, and verify password and username for our password-protected web sites. We may also communicate with a customer to provide requested services and for account-related issues via e-mail, phone or regular mail. In addition to such service and product-essential messages, we offer our customers the option to receive information about our company, related products, services and special deals. Users, however, can choose not to receive these communications from us, as set forth in the "Permission" section below.

## Children's Privacy

Our Web site is a general audience site, and we do not intentionally collect or store any personally identifiable information from children. Nevertheless, we take special precautions with children's privacy, including following the federal guidelines set by the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). In compliance with COPPA, we will not actively seek personal information about children under the age of 13 without the permission of their parent or legal guardian. If you are a parent or guardian of a child under the age of 13 and believe that child has disclosed personally identifiable information to us, you may contact us to review and request deletion of the information. For security purposes, you must provide sufficient identifying information for us to verify that you are the child's parent or guardian. At your request, we will make all reasonable efforts to delete the information provided.

## Links

Our website contain links to other sites. Worldwide Golf Shops is not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each website to which we may link that may collect personally identifiable information.

## California Privacy Rights

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, California residents have the right to request information about how we share certain kinds of personal information with third parties. California law gives you, as our customer, the right to receive the following information from us: 

* The categories of information we disclosed to third parties for their direct marketing during the preceding calendar year;

* The names and addresses of the third parties that received that information and, for any third-party business for which the name does not reveal the nature of the business, examples of the products or services marketed by that business.

We may provide this information in a standard format that is not specific to you.

## Permissions & Opt-Out Info

From time to time Worldwide Golf Shops will contact registered users with marketing or promotional emails. This is done with permission from all users messaged.

We offer visitors to Worldwide Golf Shops a means for controlling the use of session information. If, at any time after registering for information or ordering our services, you change your mind about receiving information from us or about the use of information volunteered by you, please send us a request specifying your new choice. To opt out of marketing or promotional emails to be removed. Additionally, you may call us Toll-Free at 1-888-216-5252 to modify your mail settings, including opting out from all marketing or promotional emails.

* * *

For questions about this Privacy Statement, please Contact:

Legal Department - Privacy Officer  
Worldwide Golf Shops  
1430 S. Village Way Suite T  
Santa Ana, CA 92705  
714-543-8284
